admeridian.com 2015-04-24

# Privacy Policy

### Introduction

AdMeridian.com provides a proprietary platform for marketers and agencies to buy effectively across the leading display advertising exchanges and search engines. This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices with respect to information collected in connection with the use of our platform by our clients and for use of our [www.admeridian.com](http://www.admeridian.com/) web site (the “Site”).

AdMeridian.com is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. We endeavor to adhere to all industry guidelines, and we will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to help ensure the safety and protection of consumer information.

AdMeridian.com is in compliance with the NAI’s Self-Regulatory Principles. We believe that these Principles will protect and ensure individual consumer privacy and have adopted the Principle’s guidelines and regulations.

### AdMeridian.com Data Collection on Behalf of Our Clients

In the course of delivering an ad to you, AdMeridian.com does not collect personally identifiable information about you. In other words, we do not collect information, such as your name, address, phone number, or email address. However, AdMeridian.com does collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you, such as your browser type (e.g. Firefox or Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you use (e.g. Macintosh or Windows), and whether you responded to the ad delivered. The non-personally identifiable information that we collect is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring the effectiveness of ads on behalf of AdMeridian.com customers. This non-personally identifiable information includes common information found in every communication sent over the Internet. Using this information, AdMeridian.com can infer information such as:

  1. Domain Type; Browser type (e.g., Netscape or Internet Explorer); operating system (e.g., Macintosh or Windows); browser language (e.g., Java or Unix); Internet service provider (e.g., MindSpring or AOL). We may also receive non-personally identifiable data, such as behavioral, contextual or demographics, through partnerships with online and offline 3rd party data providers.

In addition, you should be aware that AdMeridian.com works with ad serving and other companies in connection with the delivery of ads to you, and that such companies may also collect the types of non-personally identifiable information described above when you view an ad.

### About Cookies

Like most Internet sites, AdMeridian.com uses "cookies" to enhance user's experience on the Web. AdMeridian.com cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies in no way damage your system or files.

**_What are cookies and how do they enhance your Web experience?_**   
An AdMeridian.com cookie is a unique number that is assigned to you the first time we serve you an ad or identify you on a client’s website. This number is stored in a file on your computer and helps us deliver the optimal ad to you. For instance, cookies help AdMeridian.com ensure that you don't repeatedly see the same advertisement. Cookies can also help advertisers measure how you utilize an advertiser's site and the effectiveness of an advertisement. This information can then be used by advertisers to better cater to your needs. In other words, cookies help us deliver to you the types of ads in which you are more interested.

Although AdMeridian.com believes that cookies help enhance your experience on the Web by delivering more relevant messages to you, we do not need cookies to deliver ads to you. If you decline a AdMeridian.com cookie, you will still be able to view ads; however, you may see the same ad repeatedly or be delivered ads that have no relevance to you.

### How long is data stored?

AdMeridian.com sets our cookies to expire after two years and the expiration date updates every time you encounter our server. We retain the web log data for ninety days and aggregations and reports for up to three years.

### To Opt Out

Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

### About Pixels

Pixels (also known as web beacons) are used in combination with cookies to help web publishers understand how visitors interact with their web sites. A pixel is a transparent graphic image that is placed on a site. The use of a pixel allows a web site to measure the actions of the visitor opening the page that contains the pixel. AdMeridian.com may utilize clear gifs to measure visitor behavior, to help us improve visitor experience, and to manage Site content.

### AdMeridian.com Data Collection for our Corporate Site

AdMeridian.com may ask for personally identifiable information (“PII”), such as your name, address or email address, when you register for certain AdMeridian.com services that require registration and a password. We will use your PII to provide you with the service(s) you have registered for. If you provide PII to make an inquiry about our products or services, we will use that PII to respond to your inquiry. Similarly, if you are an existing customer with questions, concerns or technical support questions, we will use your PII to respond to such questions and concerns. We may send you emails describing our then-existing services or notifying you of enhancements or new services we are providing. To opt-out of such emails, you may email us at [info@admeridian.com](mailto:info@admeridian.com) . This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. We store PII on our servers in the United States. Such information is usually deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business. To update your information, please send an email to [info@admeridian.com](mailto:info@admeridian.com) This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. .

AdMeridian.com also uses non-personally identifiable information from our Web site log files to determine how you found out about us, what your interests are regarding our services, and how to further improve our site and our services.

### Disclosure

AdMeridian.com may publish or otherwise disclose anonymous, aggregate or summary information regarding our Site visitors and campaigns run on behalf of our clients. AdMeridian.com may also share non-personally identifiable end user level data collected in connection with certain advertising campaigns with the advertiser client of AdMeridian.com that is responsible for running such ad campaigns. Those are the two general ways in which we disclose information regarding our clients and end users in the normal course of our business. However in certain, unusual circumstances, we may disclose the information we have collected from end users and our clients (whether PII or non-PII), such as when we deem it necessary to protect the legal rights of AdMeridian.com or its employees, agents and contractors; protect the safety and security of visitors to our Site; protect against fraud; or to comply with the law or legal process. If AdMeridian.com sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, we may also transfer user or client information to a third party as part of that transaction.

### Security 

AdMeridian.com uses industry standard measures to safeguard data in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. No transmission of data over the Internet, however, is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of AdMeridian.com to intercept or access transmissions or communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.

### Policy Revisions

From time to time AdMeridian.com may revise this Privacy Policy. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use PII those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of the Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices.
